[
  
  {
    "question": "1. Inside which HTML element do we put the JavaScript?",
    "choice1": "<script>",
    "choice2": "<javascript>",
    "choice3": "<js>",
    "choice4": "<scripting>",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "2. What is the correct syntax for referring to an external script called 'xxx.js'?",
    "choice1": "<script href='xxx.js'>",
    "choice2": "<script name='xxx.js'>",
    "choice3": "<script src='xxx.js'>",
    "choice4": "<script file='xxx.js'>",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "3. How do you write 'Hello World' in an alert box?",
    "choice1": "msgBox('Hello World');",
    "choice2": "alertBox('Hello World');",
    "choice3": "msg('Hello World');",
    "choice4": "alert('Hello World');",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "4. Which of the following is true about variable naming conventions in JavaScript?",
    "choice1": "You should not use any of the JavaScript reserved keyword as variable name.",
    "choice2": "JavaScript variable names should not start with a numeral (0-9).",
    "choice3": "Both of the above",
    "choice4": "None of the above",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "5. Which of the following is a server-side Java Script object?",
    "choice1": "Function",
    "choice2": "File",
    "choice3": "FileUpload",
    "choice4": "Date",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "6. Which of the below is used in Java script to insert special characters?",
    "choice1": "*",
    "choice2": "\\",
    "choice3": "-",
    "choice4": "%",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "7. How does Java Script store dates in objects of Date type?",
    "choice1": "The number of days since January 1st, 1900",
    "choice2": "The number of seconds since January 1st, 1970",
    "choice3": "The number of milliseconds since January 1st, 1970",
    "choice4": "The number of picoseconds since January 1st, 1970",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "8. Which is the correct way to write a JavaScript array?",
    "choice1": "var txt = new Array(1:\"arr\",2:\"kim\",3:\"jim\")",
    "choice2": "var txt = new Array:1=(\" arr \")2=(\"kim\")3=(\"jim\")",
    "choice3": "var txt = new Array(\"arr \",\"kim\",\"jim\") ",
    "choice4": "var txt = new Array=\" arr \",\"kim\",\"jim\"",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "9. Which of the following is the tainted property of a window object in Java Script?",
    "choice1": "Pathname",
    "choice2": "Protocol",
    "choice3": "Defaultstatus",
    "choice4": "Host",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "10. Which attribute needs to be changed to make elements invisible?",
    "choice1": "visibility",
    "choice2": "visible",
    "choice3": "invisible",
    "choice4": "invisibilty",
    "answer": 1
  }
]
